So, my experience was pretty low stakes.
كانت خبرتي منخفضة للغاية.
Wrangling data for a blog post that would maybe get a few hundred views.
قد تحصل معالجة البيانات الشاملة لمقالة على مدونة على بضع مئات من المشاهدات.
But data wrangling, or more appropriately,
لكن معالجة البيانات الشاملة، أو بشكل أكثر ملاءمة،
the consequences from a lack of data wrangling,
العواقب الناجمة عن عدم وجود خلافات في البيانات،
can be serious business.
يمكن أن يكون عملاً جادًا.
For sure.
بالتأكيد.
Imagine you're a financial analyst creating models to make million dollar trades for you.
تخيل أنك محلل مالي تقوم بصنع نماذج لكسب مليون دولار من الصفقات التجارية التي تقوم بها.
Your data better be clean or you could go broke.
من الأفضل أن تكون بياناتك نظيفة أو قد تخسر.
Or imagine you're a scientist for a drug company that's about to start human trials for
أو تخيل أنك عالم تعمل بشركة أدوية على وشك البدء في إجراء تجارب على البشر
a life-saving new drug and you need to determine
للحصول على دواء جديد ينقذ الحياة وتحتاج إلى تحديد
the right dosage for humans based on your lab and animal tests.
الجرعة المناسبة للبشر بناء على اختباراتك المختبرية والحيوانية.
Your data needs to be clean or your drug
يجب أن تكون بياناتك نظيفة أو قد لا يعمل دواؤك
might not work and you could seriously hurt people.
ويمكن أن تؤذي الناس بشكل خطير.
So while you're going to get some analysis and visualization in this course.
لذا، ستحصل على بعض التحليل والمرئيات في هذه الدورة التدريبية.
It's really about getting your data ready so that
مما يجعل بياناتك جاهزة حتي يتسنى لك
anything you create is built on a solid foundation.
إعداد أي شيء على أساس متين.